# **OLAMIDE ADENIYI**

## Full Stack Web Developer

@ hello@oladev.net @ oladev.net

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a full stack web developer with 3+ years of experience and proven knowledge of programming and perseverance, through discipline and deliberate practice. I've learned to code through hard work and perseverance, through discipline and deliberate practice of conventional and modern concepts.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Applications Developer**

12/2021 - 08/2022

#### **Jetron Mall**

An e-commerce store that allows users buy and sell at ease.

 I along with a team of developers built a full stack web application with GraphQL API using modern technologies and I got relevant experiences and exposure using typescript, TTD, image processing, mail automation, PDF generation, GraphQL etc.

### Senior Full Stack Developer

06/2021 - 08/2022

## **Brigow Homes**

An online platform for people to rent, sell and lease properties such as land and houses.

- As a startup company I gained relevant experiences in teamwork, people management, human relations and other management skills.
- I also was exposed to the usage of modern technologies i.e. MERN, typescript etc.

### Full Stack Web Developer

10/2019 - 06/2021

### Gilgal House Media

A media company to cover events and post-production in a school community.

- I developed a fully scalable web application and obtained relevant experiences in data administration, hosting, web server management, CI/CD, git etc.
- I built an CBT application for the company to access new recruits based on some preset questions and interview parameters.

#### Full Stack Web Developer

12/2020 - 03/2021

#### **Hellio Solutions**

Hellio Solutions is the largest provider of Cloud Communication in Ghana and throughout the continent.

- The company was able to get more visitors and positive response on the improvement of the user interaction on the site.
- I also gained experience from implementing complex functionalities including reading a large excel file with more than 500,000 contacts in chunks and sub account authentication systems.

### Full Stack Web Developer

06/2020 - 12/2020

### Urella

A platform used by Christian congregations to handle their finances and records.

• I along with a team of web developers built a church management application with features such as attendance tracking, finance record keeping, membership authentication and data presentation and visualization.

#### Full Stack Web Developer

03/2020 - 08/2020

#### **Bytech Dynamics Investment Limited**

A real estate company with various types of rental properties.

- I developed a fully scalable web application for a real estate company with features such as tenancy automation and plan renewal and notification automation.
- The company's record-keeping accuracy increased by around 50%, which led to better decisions and management actions.

#### **STRENGTHS**

- Curiousity, Adaptability, Problem Solving, Critical thinking.
- ★ People management, Time Management, Communication skills, Leadership.

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Best Department Graduating Student 2022.

### **SKILLS**

HTML & CSS · Javascript · TailwindCSS ·

Chakra UI · Typescript · SEO · ReactJS ·

Redux · NextJS · GatsbyJS · VueJS ·

NuxtJS · Gridsome · MongoDB · Prisma ·

NodeJS · ExpressJS · Larevel/Lumen ·

 ${\sf PostgreSQL} \cdot {\sf MySQL} \cdot \\$ 

 $NoSQL/MongoDB \cdot GraphQL \cdot REST \cdot$ 

Jest · Git · Terminal · CI/CD

## LANGUAGES

English

Proficient

#### **EDUCATION**

## Electrical and Information Engineering

Landmark University 08/2017 - 07/2022

## TRAINING / COURSES

UDEMY: React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)

#### VOLUNTEERING

#### **Vice President**

Landmark University Electrical Engineering Association 08/2021 - 07/2022